From So Simple a Beginning.
Voyage of Time: Life's Journey is a documentary, drama,
history film directed by Terrence Malick.
A celebration of the universe, displaying the whole of
time, from its start to its final collapse.
This film examines all that occurred to prepare the world that stands before us now: science and
spirit, birth and death, the grand cosmos and the minute life systems of our planet.
Narrator (voice), played by Cate Blanchett.
Early Human, played by Jamal Cavil.
Early Human, played by Maisha Diatta.
Early Human, played by Yagazie Emezi.
Early Human, played by Daryl James Harris II.
Early Human, played by Sebastian Jackson.
The Chronicles of Narnia: The Voyage of the Dawn Treader is a 2010 high fantasy adventure film directed by Michael Apted from a screenplay by Christopher Markus, Stephen McFeely, and Michael
Petroni, based on the 1952 novel The Voyage of the Dawn Treader, the third published and fifth chronological novel in the children's book series The Chronicles of Narnia by C.
The sequel to The Chronicles of Narnia: Prince Caspian (2008), it is the third
and final installment in The Chronicles of Narnia film series.
It is the only film in the series not to be distributed by Walt Disney
Studios Motion Pictures, which was replaced by 20th Century Fox.
However, Disney would eventually own the rights to all the films in the series
following the acquisition of 21st Century Fox by Disney in 2019.
Georgie Henley, Skandar Keynes, Ben Barnes and Tilda Swinton reprise their
roles from the second film, with Will Poulter joining the cast.
The film is set three Narnian years after the events of Prince Caspian.
The two youngest Pevensie siblings, Edmund and Lucy, are transported
back to Narnia along with their cousin Eustace Scrubb.
They join the new king of Narnia, Caspian, in his quest to rescue seven lost
lords and save Narnia from a corrupting evil on a dark island.
Each character is tested as they journey to the
home of Aslan at the world's far end.
Development on the film began in 2007, while Prince
Caspian was still in production.
Filming was supposed to take place in Malta, the Czech Republic, and Iceland in 2008
with Michael Apted as its new director, for a planned release in 2009.
However, production was halted after a budgetary dispute between Walden Media and Walt Disney Pictures following Prince Caspian's performance at the
box office, resulting in Disney's departing the production and being replaced by 20th Century Fox under its Fox 2000 Pictures label.
Later, filming took place in Australia and New Zealand in 2009.
It is the only film in the series to be released in 3D.
The Chronicles of Narnia: The Voyage of the Dawn Treader premiered on November 30, 2010, selected for the Royal Film
Performance, before it was theatrically released on December 9 in the United Kingdom and December 10 in the United States.
The film received mixed reviews from critics.
It was a moderate success at the box office, grossing over $415.6 million
worldwide and becoming 20th Century Fox's highest-grossing film in 2010.
The song "There's a Place for Us" by Carrie Underwood was nominated
for Best Original Song at the 68th Golden Globe Awards.
An adaptation of The Silver Chair was to be the fourth entry in the film
series, but in the fall of 2011, Walden Media's contract with the C.
Lewis estate expired; the series would instead be rebooted with
the Netflix film Narnia: The Magician's Nephew.
The film explores themes of space, universe,
evolution, cosmology, search for meaning.
The tone is emotional and thought_provoking.